CONTACT:

dakarangale02@gmail.com

(+91) 7620320595

<u>LinkedIn</u> in

<u>Portfolio</u>

SKILLS

C#

C++

Python

SQL

<u>J</u>ava

Data Structures

Algorithms

C – Language

TOOLS

Unity

Game Development

Android Studio

GitHub

DHIRAJ ARUN KARANGALE

OBJECTIVE

As a C# developer, I designed and developed many 2D and 3D games. Having exposure to industrial internship in game development gained experience of closely working with other professionals. Willing to learn more and participate in real-world business projects.

EXPERIENCE

Developer, Godspeed Games

(Feb2023- Current)

- Help in developing and maintaining console app.
- Working as a programmer in Development Department at Godspeed Games.

Developer Intern, Time to School

(July2022- Feb2023)

- Help in designing and developing the edtech mobile app.
- Learn Unity, C#, AWS, APIs.

Game Developer Intern, Playhobo Games

(March2022-Aug2022)

- Developed the android game <u>Idle Crypto Miner</u> with 5k+ downloads.
- Learn Unity, C#, Azure Playfab, FB API.

Game Developer Intern, Life of Cards

(Jan2022-March2022)

• Work on 2D Android game *Pavan Putra Hanuman* with 10k+ downloads.

Jr. Developer, Ezy Helper

(Aug2021-Sept2021)

- Worked on a 3d puzzle action multiplayer game.
- Learn Unity, C# and Photon.

PROJECTS

Idle Crypto Miner 📐

- Android game with database structure in Microsoft Playfab, also provides leaderboard with FB friends.
- Crypto mining game which gives user freedom to mine bitcoin and purchase NFT in game.

Jungali Jumper 🗻

- 2D Endless Runner Android Game.
- Integrated with Database, Leaderboard, Ads.

Be Fit 📐

- Fitness Android App.
- Made with Android Studio, Java and XML.

Really Sqube 📐

- 2D Platformer Android Game.
- Integrated with Ads, Enemy AI.

EDUCATION

- B. E in Computer Engineering: Sinhgad College of Engineering, Pune (GPA 8.18) 2022 3rd Year
- HSC: J. V. Mehta Jr. College, Khamgaon (77.08%) 2019 2020
- SSC: Saraswati Vidya Mandir, Khamgaon (81.60 %) 2017 2018